Bye to the boring
Bye Cara berpikir kolot
Bye 退屈な
Bye 따분한
Bye ความน่าเบื่อ
Bye 枯燥乏味
Bye sự buồn chán
Rigid way of thinking
Yang membosankan
真面目すぎるそんな考え方
고지식한 그런 사고방식
แนวคิดที่เข้มงวดเช่นนี้
那种死板的思维方式
死板的那種思考模式
Cách tư duy ngay thẳng đó
Say what you really mean
Say apa yang ingin sebenarnya ingin kau katakan
Say 素直な心だけ
Say 솔직한 마음만
Say สิ่งที่อยู่ในใจจริงๆ
Say 真实的想法
Say 最真實的心情
Say tấm lòng ngay thẳng
Don't lie to yourself
Jangan menipu diri sendiri
自分自身を騙さないで
너를 속이진 마
อย่าหลอกตัวเอง
不要骗你自己
別再欺騙你自己
Đừng dối trá bản thân
You and me
Our dreams are just drawn different
Hanya menggambar mimpi yang berbeda
違う夢を描いているだけ
다른 꿈을 그릴 뿐이지
เราอาจจะวาดภาพความฝันที่ต่างกันออกไป
只是描绘着不同的梦而已
只是描繪不一樣的夢而已
Chỉ là đôi bên có hai giấc mơ khác nhau
But you and me
Keep believing
I Live My Life
Break out from the box
Sekarang aku melanggar
これから私は型通りの
이제 난 틀에 맞춰진
ออกจากกรอบ
如今我要打破
此刻起我要破壞
Luật lệ trong khuôn khổ
That defined me
aturan yang telah ditetapkan
ルールをぶち壊す
규칙 깨버려
และกฎเกณฑ์เดิมๆ ที่กำหนดตัวฉัน
那些条条框框
框架下的規則
Giờ đây em phá vỡ
Your obvious way of thinking
Cara berpikirmu yang jelas
ありきたりな君の考え方
뻔한 네 사고방식
วิธีคิดที่ชัดเจนของเธอ
你那俗套的思维方式
你老套的思考模式
Cách tư duy dễ biết của anh
I Live My Life
Now it truly begins
Ini adalah awalnya
これからがスタート
이제부터가 시작이야
จากนี้ไปคือจุดเริ่มต้น
现在才是开始
現在才是開始
Giờ mới là bắt đầu thôi
This life I've chosen
Aku adalah
私が選んだ
내가 선택한
ชีวิตที่ฉันเลือกเอง
我选择的
我選擇的
Nhân vật chính trong cuộc sống
And I, as a main character
Tokoh utama dari kehidupan yang kupilih
人生の主人公は私
삶의 주인공은 나
ที่ฉันคือตัวละครหลัก
人生的主人公是我
人生主角是我自己
Mà em tự chọn chính là em
Betcha I'll Live My Life
Menantikan Live My Life
楽しみにして Live My Life
기대해 Live My Life
รอดูเลย Live My Life
期待吧 Live My Life
Hãy đợi đấy Live my life
Brand new I'll Live My Life
Membarui Live My Life
新しく Live My Life
새롭게 Live My Life
เริ่มใหม่ Live My Life
全新的 Live My Life
Thật mới lạ Live my life
Oh, all out, Live My Life
Oh Dengan kuat Live My Life
Oh 力強く Live My Life
Oh 힘차게 Live My Life
Oh เปี่ยมด้วยพลัง Live My Life
Oh 用力地 Live My Life
Oh mạnh mẽ lên Live my life
Say it loud, Live My Life
Teriak Live My Life
叫んで Live My Life
외쳐봐 Live My Life
ตะโกนออกไป Live My Life
呐喊吧 Live My Life
大聲喊 Live My Life
Hãy la lên Live my life
Keep shining, bright Eyes
Keep Eyes yang bersinar
Keep 輝く Eyes
Keep 빛나는 Eyes
Keep Eyes ที่ส่องแสง
Keep 闪亮的 Eyes
Keep 發光的 Eyes
Keep long lanh Eyes
Better idea
That confident look
Raut wajah yang percaya diri
自信のある表情
자신 있는 표정
สีหน้าที่มั่นใจ
自信的表情
充滿自信的表情
Nét mặt tự tin
Lightly moving, we're changing
Perubahan bergerak Lighty
Lightly 動き出す変化
Lightly 움직이는 변화
Lightly การเปลี่ยนแปลงที่เปลี่ยนไป
Lightly 改变的变化
Lightly 改變的變化
Lightly sự thay đổi đang diễn ra
Make it a new thing
Yeah, start another new beginning
Ya, ini permulaan yang lain
そう また新しい始まりだよ
그래 또 다른 시작이야
ใช่แล้ว การเริ่มต้นใหม่อีกครั้ง
没错 又是另一个开始
沒錯 又是另一個開始
Đúng vậy, là sự khởi đầu mới đó
You and me
you and me
Felt like we were in different dreams
Rasanya seperti bermimpi hal yang berbeda
違う夢を見るようだった
다른 꿈을 꾸는 듯했지
เหมือนเรามีความฝันที่แตกต่างกัน
仿佛做了不一样的梦
就像做了不同的夢
Giống như đang mơ giấc mơ khác
But you and me
but you and me
Keep believing
keep believing
I Live My Life
Break out from the box
Sekarang aku melanggar
これから私は型通りの
이제 난 틀에 맞춰진
ออกจากกรอบ
如今我要打破
此刻起我要破壞
Luật lệ trong khuôn khổ
That defined me
aturan yang telah ditetapkan
ルールをぶち壊す
규칙 깨버려
และกฎเกณฑ์เดิมๆ ที่กำหนดตัวฉัน
那些条条框框
框架下的規則
Giờ đây em phá vỡ
Your obvious way of thinking
Cara berpikirmu yang jelas
ありきたりな君の考え方
뻔한 네 사고방식
วิธีคิดที่ชัดเจนของเธอ
你那俗套的思维方式
你老套的思考模式
Cách tư duy dễ biết của anh
I Live My Life
Now it truly begins
Ini adalah awalnya
これからがスタート
이제부터가 시작이야
จากนี้ไปคือจุดเริ่มต้น
现在才是开始
現在才是開始
Giờ mới là bắt đầu thôi
This life I've chosen
Aku adalah
私が選んだ
내가 선택한
ชีวิตที่ฉันเลือกเอง
我选择的
我選擇的
Nhân vật chính trong cuộc sống
And I, as a main character
Tokoh utama dari kehidupan yang kupilih
人生の主人公は私
삶의 주인공은 나
ที่ฉันคือตัวละครหลัก
人生的主人公是我
人生主角是我自己
Mà em tự chọn chính là em
Betcha I'll Live My Life
Menantikan Live My Life
楽しみにして Live My Life
기대해 Live My Life
รอดูเลย Live My Life
期待吧 Live My Life
Hãy đợi đấy Live my life
(Things can be hard sometimes)
(Meski terkadang sulit)
(時には辛くても)
(때론 힘들어도)
(ถึงแม้จะยากลำบากบ้างในบางครั้ง)
(就算时而疲倦)
(就算時而疲倦)
(Đôi khi dù mệt mỏi)
Brand new I'll Live My Life
Membarui Live My Life
新しく Live My Life
새롭게 Live My Life
เริ่มใหม่ Live My Life
全新的 Live My Life
Thật mới lạ Live my life
(But it'll come to us, that precious Light)
(Light berharga yang datang kepadaku)
(私に訪れる大切な Light)
(나에게 찾아오는 소중한 Light)
(Light อันล้ำค่าที่เข้ามาหาฉัน)
(眷顾我的珍贵的 Light)
(也會來找我的珍貴的 Light)
(Light điều quý giá tìm đến em)
Oh, all out, Live My Life
Oh Dengan kuat Live My Life
Oh 力強く Live My Life
Oh 힘차게 Live My Life
Oh เปี่ยมด้วยพลัง Live My Life
Oh 用力地 Live My Life
Oh mạnh mẽ lên Live my life
(Don't give up, believe in yourself)
(Don't give up Percayalah dirimu sendiri)
(Don’t give up 自分を信じて)
(Don’t give up 자신을 믿어)
(Don't give up เชื่อมั่นในตัวเอง)
(Don't give up 相信自己)
(Don't give up hãy tin vào chính mình)
Say it loud, Live My Life
Teriak Live My Life
叫んで Live My Life
외쳐봐 Live My Life
ตะโกนออกไป Live My Life
呐喊吧 Live My Life
大聲喊 Live My Life
Hãy la lên Live my life
(So precious, it's Your life)
(Your life yang berharga)
(大切な Your life)
(소중한 Your life)
(Your life ที่ล้ำค่า)
(珍贵的 Your life)
(珍貴的 Your life)
(Your life quý giá)
Can't stop time and Life's too short
Waktu tidak dapat dihentikan Life’s too short
時間は止められないでしょう Life’s too short
시간은 멈출 수 없잖아 Life’s too short
เวลาไม่มีวันหยุดเดิน Life's too short
时间不能停止 Life's too short
畢竟時間不會停下 Life's too short
Thời gian không ngừng được Life's too short
No more, I don’t care
No more, I don't care
Don't tie me down
Tolong jangan mengekangku
束縛しないで
구속하지 말아줘
โปรดอย่ารั้งฉันไว้
不要把我束缚
不要把我限制住
Đừng ràng buộc em
There's no right answer to life, You know best
Tiada jawaban benar dalam hidup You know best
人生に正解なんてない You know best
인생에 정답이란 없어 You know best
ชีวิตไม่มีคำตอบที่ถูกต้อง You know best
人生没有正确答案 You know best
人生沒有所謂正確答案 You know best
Cuộc đời không có đáp án nào là đúng You know best
You just live your life
True to myself, that's how I'll live
'Ku akan hidup sebagai diriku sendiri
私は私らしく生きていくわ
나답게 난 살 거야
ฉันจะใช้ชีวิตแบบเป็นตัวของฉันเอง
我要活出自我
我要活得像自己
Em sẽ sống đúng với bản thân em
I Live My Life
I'm not scared anymore
Sekarang aku tidak takut
もう私は恐れない
이제 난 두렵지 않아
ตอนนี้ฉันไม่กลัวอะไรอีกแล้ว
如今我不再畏惧
從此我不再害怕
Giờ đây không còn sợ hãi nữa
No hesitating
Jangan ragu
躊躇しないで
주저하지 마
อย่ามัวลังเล
不要犹豫
別再躊躇不前
Đừng chần chừ do dự
Life is like a miracle
I Live My Life
Real life begins now
Mulai sekarang, inilah kenyataan
これからが本物よ
이제부터가 진짜야
จากนี้ไปคือการใช้ชีวิตที่แท้จริง
现在开始才是真的
現在起才是真的
Từ giờ mới là thật đấy
With me, as a main character in a happy life
Akulah tokoh utama dalam kehidupan yang bahagia
私が幸せになる人生の主人公は私
내가 행복할 삶의 주인공은 나
และฉันเองคือตัวละครหลักของชึวิตที่มีความสุข
我幸福人生的主人公是我
我幸福人生的主角是自己
Cuộc sống hạnh phúc này nhân vật chính là em
Betcha I'll Live My Life
Menantikan Live My Life
楽しみにして Live My Life
기대해 Live My Life
รอดูเลย Live My Life
期待吧 Live My Life
Hãy đợi đấy Live my life
Brand new I'll Live My Life
Membarui Live My Life
新しく Live My Life
새롭게 Live My Life
เริ่มใหม่ Live My Life
全新的 Live My Life
Thật mới lạ Live my life
Oh, all out, Live My Life
Oh Dengan kuat Live My Life
Oh 力強く Live My Life
Oh 힘차게 Live My Life
Oh เปี่ยมด้วยพลัง Live My Life
Oh 用力地 Live My Life
Oh mạnh mẽ lên Live my life
Say it loud, Live My Life
Teriak Live My Life
叫んで Live My Life
외쳐봐 Live My Life
ตะโกนออกไป Live My Life
呐喊吧 Live My Life
大聲喊 Live My Life
Hãy la lên Live my life
Life